

My web portfolio

### Contact:

Mcomendoza.92@gmail.com

+34644053023

Social Media:

Linkedin, Github

### LANGUAGES SKILLS

Native: Spanish

**English: Professional** 

## **FRONTEND**

Typescript, JavaScript, NextJS, React, CSS, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Radix UI.

### **BACKEND**

Node JS, Python, Express, and ORM

### **DATA BASES**

Mongo DB, PostgreSQL, mySQL, Supabase, NeonDb.

### **DESIGN**

Figma, Full Responsive design, UX and UI experience. Corel draw and adobe XD for fiting images and videos.

### **SOFT SKILLS**

Git, GitHub, JIRA, Trello, Scurm, Kanban, Agile,

### **TESTING**

Unit Testing, jest chai mocha react testing library

### **OTHER INTERSTING FACTS**

Full Stack Developer (2021)
Proficiency in **CRM** and **ERP** platforms
Salesforce/Hubspot/ SAP
R3/Odoo/Oracle WMS Cloud

### **WORKING SKILLS**

Strategic Thinking and Global Vision. Ethics, honesty and responsibility. Flexibility and adaptability. Enjoy solving problems. Teamwork and proactivity. Initiative and curiosity. Multitasking and adaptability to

# **NICOLAS MENDOZA**

I am a developer with 3 years of experience creating custom web solutions and custom applications. I have worked on various projects, including inventory management systems, financial management platforms, e-commerce applications and landing pages. During my career, I have applied various technologies and worked under agile methodologies such as Scrum, collaborating in multidisciplinary teams with tools such as JIRA, Git and GitHub. My focus is on developing efficient solutions aligned with business needs, ensuring timely and high-quality deliveries.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### SaaS builded

2024 - current

# Management System - info

**Technologies:** Next JS – typescript – Prisma, Neon, clerk, SSR, NodeJs.

The platform allows you to generate detailed reports, view interactive graphs and receive real-time notifications. It is designed to optimize business management and provide key decision-making tools. In addition, it is intuitive and adaptable to the specific needs of users.

### Full Stack Developer – <u>ALLCOT GROUP</u>

Jun 2022 to April 2024

Implementation of carbon credit platform with IT team

Typescript, JavaScript, Node JS with React as main framework.

Work review and sprint management in projects.

Use of agile methodologies to achieve project objectives and deliverables.

Use of JIRA for project management.

Use of relational (SQL) and non-relational (MongoDB) databases.

Management of AWS cloud (s3bucket).

Use of Git and GitHub to upload and update projects in different branches

# Assistant tutor - Rolling Code Argentina

2021 -6 months

Assistant tutor in programming school

JS, HTML and CSS review and support

Work review and sprint management in projects.

Use of AGILE methodologies for project management.

Content creation for classes

Use of GitHub for task tracking and Trello for student tracking.

## My Freelance- projects

## <u>Inventory Management – ERP system</u>

**Technologies:** Next JS – Mongo DB – NodeJs - Express

Creation of a web application for inventory management of carbon credits adjusted for a specific company, tracking transactions (purchase/sale), downloads, users and customer data.

## **Bakery**

**Technologies:** React JS, Node, Mongo, CSS+, Bootstrap – API REST E-commerce creation for Pastry Shop, administration panel and web order management (dates, delivery, stripe payments).

# ACADEMIC TRAINING

**Degree & Master in Industrial Engineer -** 2014-2019 **National University of Tucumán- Argentina** UNT

Full Stack Web developer Rolling Code School - 2020-2023
MERN Stack Certificate
Bootcamp Python PRO
Python Certificate